RAFI REZAN

Depok, Jawa Barat, 16461 | +6289658895449 rafirezan@gmail.com | linkedin: RAFI REZAN

ABOUT ME

I graduated from the University of Dirgantara Marsekal Suryadarma, majoring in Industrial Engineering. Having professional and academic experience in industrial such as theoretical and practical knowledge related to industrial and its derivation has been really familiar to me. Beside of that, I active in internal and external organizations. At the end of my studies, I was able to adapt to the world of work. So I can do work at the same time as college. However, I managed to graduate on time with a 3.41 GPA. I can operate Microsoft Office and technical drawing software. I'm a disciplined and high motivated person. Also capable to solve problems in general and excel at both individual or team work. Lastly, being an adaptable person is also one of my strongest traits which I expect will help me a lot to be a well-functioning employee in my future workplace.

EDUCATION

University of Dirgantara Marsekal Suryadarma Bachelor Industrial Engineering | GPA 3,41/4.00

2017 - 2021

STATE VOCATIONAL SCHOOL 1 DEPOK

2014 - 2017

ACHIEVEMENT

1st WINNER August 2016

Football competition between students in the KODIM area 0508/Depok

2nd **WINNER** October 2014

Indonesian Education League for Vocational High School in the Indonesian Education League Football Competition

1st WINNER April 2013

Football Sports in Depok City in the Depok City Sports Week Football Competition

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Global Digital Niaga, Jakarta

Warehouse Operator

July 2021 - July 2022

- Package of product
- Held stock opname in warehouse
- Product handover to collaborative logistics

PT. Nusa Indah Jaya Utama, Bekasi

Production Internship

December 2020 - March 2021

- Final product checking
- Help production process such as planning production raw materials preparation

PT. NGK Busi Indonesia, Jakarta

Production Internship

July 2015 – October 2015

- Final product checking
- Help production process such as planning production raw materials preparation

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Indonesian Industrial Engineering Student Association, Jakarta Zone

PSDM Staff

December 2018 – November 2019

Looking for future candidats members and holding discussion group forums.

Industrial Engineering Student Association, UNSURYA

Public Relation

September 2018 – September 2019

- As an intermediary between organizations and the outside community.
- Inform important information to members of the organization.
- Build relationships with internal and external organizations.
- Managing social media and email.

ADDITIONAL

Technical: Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, Powerpoint), Auto CAD

Soft Skill: public speaking, leadership, teamwork

Hard Skill: Data Analyst

Language: Indonesian and English

Driver License: A and C